Who is it
Daniel why are you here
Sis
I'm looking for brother-in-law
Brother-in-law
Between us before
there might be a misunderstanding
It's all Zane's fault that jerk
I was blinded by him
How about this
come back and work for me
I'll give you a raise
Three thousand a month
Five thousand
Daniel
Are you really dumb
or just playing dumb
Doing it on my own
selling just one batch
nets me over two million
Why would I earn 5,000 at your place
Because you are shameless
We are family
Do you have to be so calculative
Yes
I wasn't calculative enough before
So I was foolish enough
to work for you for two years
From now on don't expect
to take any advantage of me
Daniel
What you did before was way out of line
Now saying a few nice words
and you want him to go back
Nothing in this world is that easy
Fine
Turning down my goodwill huh
I don't believe without you
I can't raise frogs well
Just you wait
One day
you'll come begging me